https://www.nailers.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Sign In To Your Account
Forgot Password
Don't Have An Account?
You should, it gets you this:
Faster Checkout with saved details
Easy order tracking and order histories
Notification of new products as they become available
We just need your email address and a password to get started...
SHOPPING BASKET
There is nothing in your basket.
Continue
Checkout
CategoriesNailersTYPEBrad NailersCordlessFlooringCoilFramingFine Wire PinnersBRANDSAce & KFascoOmerPaslodeIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk CloseStaplersTYPE71 Type80 Type90 Type92 Type97 TypeM2FencingCarton ClosingWide CrownBRANDSAce & KFascoOmerPaslodeIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk CloseFasteningsNAILS23G Pins/Brads21G Pins/Brads18G Pins/Brads16G Pins/Brads15G Pins/BradsT NailsCoil Nails21° Framing Nails34° Framing NailsCleat NailsPPN NailsScrail Coil FastenersScrail Framing FastenersSTAPLES71 Type80 Type97 Type90 Type92 TypeM2FencingCarton ClosingWide CrownSPECIALISTFlexi TabsCorrugatedPolymer (Plastic)If you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk CloseAir CompressorsTYPEDirect DriveBelt DrivePetrolScrewBRANDSBamaxNardiFiniIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk CloseHose/Ring MainTYPEHose AssemblyQuick Release Adapters & Couplings For HoseAir Line FittingsAir Ring Main SystemsFilter Regulators & LubricatorsIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk CloseLightingSCANGRIP LIGHTINGChargers, Adapters and BatteriesColour MatchCordlessDual SystemsFloodlightsHandheldHeadlampsInspection LightsExplosion ProofMainsTripods & BracketsNEBOBattery PoweredRechargeableIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk ClosePPETYPEEar ProtectionEye ProtectionIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk CloseToolsFELOBits & Bit HoldersFor ElectriciansHand ToolsHex and Torx L KeysPliersScrewdriversScrewdriver Tool SetsT-Handle ToolsIf you can’t find what you are looking for, please contact a member of our team on 01707 282700 or sales@nailers.co.uk ClosePaslode & SPIT Products
Free delivery on all orders over £100
Click & Collect for free in just 1 minute
Privacy Policy
As a result of the new General Data Protection Regulation (known as GDPR) that comes into effect on 25 May 2018 we have produced a privacy notice to inform our customers how we use any data that you give us or any that we may collect from you.  It applies to all products and services, and instances where we collect your personal data.
This privacy notice applies to personal information processed by Alpha Pneumatic Supplies.
Our Data Protection Officer
We have a  data protection officer (“DPO”). You can contact the DPO using the contact details at the end of this notice.
What kinds of personal information about you do we process?
Personal information that we’ll process in connection with our products and services, if relevant, includes:
Personal and contact details, such as business name, contact personnel name and contact details, address, telephone numbers, email address, website address
Records of products you or your business have purchased from us
What is the source of your personal information?
We’ll collect personal information from the following general sources:
From you directly
Information generated about you when you use our products and services
What do we use your data for?
We use your personal data for the following purposes:
To send you products you have specified to addresses you have specified
To service and repair your tools as requested by you
For direct marketing communications and related profiling to help us to offer you relevant products and services, including deciding whether or not to offer you certain products and services. We may send marketing to you by SMS, email, phone, post, social media and digital channels .
To provide insight and analysis of our customers to enable us to improve products or services, or to assess or improve the operating of our business
Do we share your personal information with other organisations?
No – we never share your information with the any third parties: other than providing information to key suppliers to enable your warranty and other repairs to be handled effectively.
How and when can you withdraw your consent?
You can withdraw your consent for us to process your personal data at any time by contacting us using the contact details at the end of this notice.
Is your personal information transferred outside the UK or the EEA?
No
What are your rights under data protection laws?
Here is a list of the rights that all individuals have under data protection laws. They don’t apply in all circumstances. The right of data portability is only relevant from May 2018.
The right to be informed about the processing of your personal information
The right to have your personal information corrected if it is inaccurate and to have incomplete personal information completed
The right to object to processing of your personal information
The right to restrict processing of your personal information
The right to have your personal information erased (the “right to be forgotten”)
The right to request access to your personal information and to obtain information about how we process it
The right to move, copy or transfer your personal information (“data portability”)
Rights in relation to automated decision making which has a legal effect or otherwise significantly affects you
You have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office which enforces data protection laws: https://ico.org.uk/. You can contact us using the contact details at the end of this notice.
Your right to object
You have the right to object to certain purposes for processing, in particular to data processed for direct marketing purposes and to data processed for certain reasons based on our legitimate interests. Contact us to exercise these rights.
What are your marketing preferences and what do they mean?
We may use your home address, phone numbers, email address and social media or digital channels to contact you according to your marketing preferences. You can stop our marketing at any time by contacting us using the contact details at the end of this notice or by following the instructions in the communication.
Cookies Policy
This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping baskets, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsers
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy notice, or if you wish to exercise your rights or contact the DPO, please contact:
DATA PROTECTION OFFICER
ALPHA PNEUMATIC SUPPLIES LTD
UNIT 7, THE iO CENTRE
HATFIELD BUSINESS PARK
HATFIELD
HERTS, AL10 9EW
TEL          01707 282700
EMAIL    sales@alphapneumatics.co.uk
This website or its third party tools use cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and required to achieve the purposes illustrated in the cookie policy. If you want to know more or withdraw your consent to all or some of the cookies, please refer to the cookie policy. By closing this banner, scrolling this page, clicking a link or continuing to browse otherwise, you agree to the use of cookies. Find out more.OK
